Guide to the Frank H. T. Rhodes papers,1977-1996.
Rhodes, Frank H. T. papers, 1977-1996.
- Series XI. 1987-1988
  - Subject Files
    - Higher Education
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1970-88 (Box 184, Folder 39-44)
        Cabot, Louis W.; Silber, John R.; Randel, Don M.; Racker, Efraim; Status of minority graduate students; Freedom of Expression at Yale.
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1970-88 (Box 185, Folder 1-3)
        Spies, Richard R.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Bowen, William G.
      - State Education Department, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 4)
      - Institutional Neutrality, 1974-88 (Box 185, Folder 5-6)
        Bok, Derek; Nuclear arms race; Divestment; Boycotts; Freedom of expression.
      - Rhodes Scholarship, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Universities
      - SUNY, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 8-11)
        Johnstone, D. Bruce; Komisar, Jerome B.
      - SUNY, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 12)
        Joint meeting of SUNY and Cornell Trustees.
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 13-17)
        Moscow State University.
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 18-20)
        Murphy, Joseph; University of Puerto Rico; ROTC-type teaching fellowships; Undergraduate Summer Exchange for Minority Students; RPI/ Cornell Center for Design Research.
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 21)
        Kennedy, Donald; Sterling, J. E. Wallace; Bok, Derek C.; Civil disobedience; Unions.
      - SUNY, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 22)
    - Student Life
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 23)
        Outrage Magazine; Cornell Lunatic.
    - Campus Affairs
      - Incidents - Sexual Abuse, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 24-25)
        Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity.
      - Incidents, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 26)
        Purcell, Robert W.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Trustee Incident; Minority student support; Divestment.
      - Incidents, 1986-88 (Box 185, Folder 27-32)
        Divestment protests; Faculty protests; Hunger strike.
    - Commencement
      - Baccalaureate, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 33)
      - General, 1987-88 (Box 185, Folder 34-35)
- Series XII. 1988-1989
  - Presidential/Administrative
    - Office of the President
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 185, Folder 36)
      - General, 1988 (Box 185, Folder 37)
      - General, 1987-89 (Box 185, Folder 38)
      - General, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 39)
      - General, 1982-85 (Box 185, Folder 40)
        Ashby, Eric.
      - General, 1982 (Box 185, Folder 41)
        Mingde, Li.
      - General, 1985-86 (Box 185, Folder 42)
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 185, Folder 43)
      - General, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 44)
      - General, 1988 (Box 185, Folder 45)
      - General, 1988 (Box 185, Folder 46)
      - Condolences, 1988-89 (Box 185, Folder 47)
      - Congratulations, 1988 (Box 185, Folder 48)
      - Congratulations, 1988-89 (Box 185, Folder 49)
      - Congratulations, 1988 (Box 185, Folder 50)
      - Congratulations, 1988-89 (Box 185, Folder 51)
      - Congratulations, 1988-89 (Box 185, Folder 52)
      - Congratulations, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - Professors Emeritus, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - Invitations, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 3)
      - Staff Writer, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 4)
        Bart, Connie
      - Affirmative Action, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 5-7)
      - Presidential Councillors, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 8)
      - Presidents Emeritus, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 9)
        Willard Straight takeover
      - General Contact, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 10)
      - Community Contact, 1988 (Box 186, Folder 11)
      - Department Contact, 1988 (Box 186, Folder 12)
      - Faculty Contact, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 13)
        Women Faculty
      - Student Contact, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 14)
      - Site Visits, 1984 (Box 186, Folder 15)
      - Judicial Advisor, 1979-85 (Box 186, Folder 16)
      - Judicial Advisor Search, 1981 (Box 186, Folder 17)
      - Judicial Advisor Search, 1983 (Box 186, Folder 18)
      - Judicial Advisor Search, 1985 (Box 186, Folder 19)
      - Judicial Advisor Search, 1979-80 (Box 186, Folder 20)
      - Judicial Advisor Search, 1979 (Box 186, Folder 21)
      - Judicial Advisor Search, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 22-23)
      - Ombudsman Search, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 24)
      - Social Events, 1988 (Box 186, Folder 25-26)
      - Social Events, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 27-28)
      - Social Events, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 29-30)
      - Social Events - Willard Straight Takeover., 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 31-32)
    - Executive Staff
      - Mini-Retreat, 1988 (Box 186, Folder 33)
    - Senior Vice President
      - General, 1989 (Box 186, Folder 34-35)
      - Upstate Roundtable on Manufacturing and Economic Development, 1989 (Box 186, Folder 36-37)
      - Budget, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 38-42)
      - Office of Human Resources, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 43-45)
      - Human Resource Development, 1989 (Box 186, Folder 46)
      - Office of Human Resources - Collective Bargaining, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 47)
      - Office of Human Resources - Fringe Benefits, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 48)
      - Office of Human Resources - Degree Programs for University Staff, 1988 (Box 186, Folder 49)
      - Office of Human Resources - Middle Management, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 50)
      - Office of Human Resources - Policies and Procedures, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 51)
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1988-89 (Box 186, Folder 52-53)
        Lynah fan behavior; football.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1988 (Box 187, Folder 1)
      - Physical Education and Athletics - Football Problem., 1989 (Box 187, Folder 2-4)
        Baughan, Maxie; Weiss, Roger J.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 5)
      - Controller, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 6-8)
      - Budget Office, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 9-13)
      - Endowment Payout Rate, 1988 (Box 187, Folder 14)
      - Bursar's Office, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 15)
      - Payroll Office, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 16)
      - University Auditor, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - University Counsel
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 18-20)
        Derrick, Darron; Relihan, Walter J.
      - Cornell Heights, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 21-22)
      - Indemnification, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 23)
        Harr, Sidney B.
    - Treasurer and Vice President
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 24-26)
      - Indirect Costs, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 27-29)
      - Capital Funding and Priorities Committee, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 30)
    - Vice President for Campus Affairs
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 31-33)
        Off campus housing
      - Willard Straight Takeover - 20th Anniversary, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 34)
      - Campus Store, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 35)
      - Center for Religion, Ethics and Social Policy, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 36)
      - CURW, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 37-38)
      - Dean of Students, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 39-40)
      - Fraternities and Sororities, 1988-89 (Box 187, Folder 41-44)
      - Policy Digest, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Dining, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Housing, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 3-10)
        Cornell University Strategic Housing Plan
      - International Student Office, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 11)
      - Department of Public Safety, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 12-13)
        Moreno, Ofir
      - Contingency Planning and Policies, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 14-15)
      - Transportation, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 16-19)
        Comprehensive Parking and Transportation Plan for the 80s
      - University Health Services, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 20)
      - AIDS - Drugs - Drug Free Work Place, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 21)
      - University Unions, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 22)
        Department of Unions and Activities
    - Vice President for Facilities and Business Operations
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 23)
        Campus grounds
      - Critical Maintenance, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 24)
      - Energy Conservation, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 25)
      - Department of Environment Conservation, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 26)
      - Insurance, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 27)
      - Life Safety Services, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 28)
      - Materials Management, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 29)
      - Planning and Facilities, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 30)
      - Roberts and Wing Halls, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 31)
      - Tjaden Hall, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 32)
      - Stimson Hall, Savage Farm, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 33)
      - Martha Van Rensselaer Hall, Arts Quad, Sage, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 34)
      - Real Estate, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 35)
      - Catholic Properties Study, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 36)
      - Telecommunications, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 37)
      - Travel Office, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 38)
    - Vice President for Public Affairs
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 39-40)
      - Proposed Public Affairs Commitments, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 41)
      - Reunion, 1989, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 42-43)
      - Alumni, Homecoming 1988, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 44-46)
      - Alumni General - Alumni Letter, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 47-49)
      - Alumni Document, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 50)
      - Alumni, Class of 1959, Gateway Challenge, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 51)
      - Cornell Alumni News, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 52)
      - Cornell Adult University, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 53)
      - Alumni Trips, 1988-89 (Box 188, Folder 54-57)
      - Alumni Trips - West Coast, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 1-3)
      - Alumni Trips - Chicago, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - Committee on Memorials, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 5)
      - Cornell Fund, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Cornell University Council, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 7-8)
      - Cornell University Council Election, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 9)
      - Development Miscellaneous, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 10-16)
        Merrill, Philip
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 17)
        125th Anniversary
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 18)
        Dyson, John S.; Milstein, Howard; Seymour, Howard.
      - Development, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 19)
        DeFrees, Barbara Baldwin
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 20)
        Marler, Peter R.
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 21)
        Merrill, Philip; Kiplinger, Austin
      - Meeting with Deans and Executive Staff, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 22)
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 23)
        Greenawalt, Crawford H.
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 24)
        Brown, Minnie Miller; Kroch Library
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 25)
      - Building Cornell's Future, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 26-29)
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 30-33)
        Lilienthal, Alfred
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 34-35)
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 36)
        Lee, Benson; Cornell Recognition Project
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 37)
        Kaneb, Al; Kroch, Carl A.
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 38-40)
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 41)
        Campaign planning
      - Development - Gifts, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 42-44)
      - Development, 1988-89 (Box 189, Folder 45)
        Hatfield Fund
      - Development, 1984 (Box 189, Folder 46)
        Clark, James; Performing Arts Center
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 189, Folder 47-51)
        Dean, Arthur; Hertzberg, Benjamin; Johnson, Samuel C.
      - Development, 1984 (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
        Johnson Graduate School of Management
      - Development, 1985 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 190, Folder 5)
        Lake, Charles W.
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 190, Folder 6)
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 190, Folder 7)
        Olin, Spencer T.
      - Development, 1984-86 (Box 190, Folder 8)
        Robison, Ellis H.
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 190, Folder 9)
        Snee, Katherine
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - Development, 1984-85 (Box 190, Folder 11)
      - Glee Club, 1989 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Vice President for University Relations
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 13-16)
      - Electronic Delivery, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 17)
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 18-20)
      - Cat Flap - The Final Chapter, 1989 (Box 190, Folder 21-22)
        Okamoto, Michiko
      - Divestment Complaint Letters, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 23)
      - Segal, Sam, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 24)
      - Peer Review, 1986-88 (Box 190, Folder 25-26)
      - Bartels Fellowship, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 27)
      - Community Relations, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 28-29)
      - Siegel and Gale Report and Responses, 1987-88 (Box 190, Folder 30-31)
      - Cornell Chronicle, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 32)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 33)
      - Federal Relations, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 34-37)
      - Federal Relations- Presidential Scholar Letters to Legislators, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 38)
      - Federal Relations -Trade Bill Letters, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 39)
      - Federal Relations - Bush, George, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 40)
      - Federal Relations - Quayle, Dan, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 41)
      - Federal Relations - Meeting of Selected University Presidents with President-Elect Bush, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 42)
      - State Relations, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 43-46)
      - State Relations - Meeting with Legislators in Albany, 1989 (Box 190, Folder 47)
      - State Relations - Lt. Governor's Task Force on Research Funding, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 48)
      - State Relations - General, 1988-89 (Box 190, Folder 49)
        Supercomputer funding
      - Public Information/News Bureau, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous News Releases, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 2-4)
      - News Bureau - Director Search, 1989 (Box 191, Folder 5)
      - University Publications, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 6)
        Gates, Henry Louis
      - President's Annual Report, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - Environmental Health and Safety, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 8-9)
      - Environmental Health and Safety - Review Council, 1983 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Cornell University Medical College
      - Correspondence, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 11)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Code of Professional Conduct, 1988 (Box 191, Folder 12)
      - Cornell University Medical College, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 13-15)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Proposed Queens Medical School, 1988 (Box 191, Folder 16)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Cabaret, 1988 (Box 191, Folder 17)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Accreditation Report, 1989 (Box 191, Folder 18)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Accreditation Team, 1978 (Box 191, Folder 19-20)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Strategic Planning, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 21-24)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Budget and Finances, 1988 (Box 191, Folder 25)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Board of Overseers, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 26)
      - Cornell University Medical College - Joint Board, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 27)
      - Society of the New York Hospital, 1989 (Box 191, Folder 28)
      - Cornell University Medical College - New York Hospital - Long-Range Planning Document, 1982 (Box 191, Folder 29)
    - Trustees
      - University By-Laws, 1989 (Box 191, Folder 30)
      - Trustees - General, 1987-89 (Box 191, Folder 31-32)
      - Trustees - Pat Stewart/Lilyan Affinito, 1989 (Box 191, Folder 33)
      - Trustees - Correspondence, 1988-89 (Box 191, Folder 34-35)
      - Trustees- General and Correspondence, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Trustees - Buildings and Properties Committee, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 2-5)
      - Trustees - Cornell Corporate Liaison Committee, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 6-10)
      - Trustee - Development Steering Committee, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 11-16)
      - Trustees - Investment Committee, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 17-29)
        Divestment
      - Trustees - Proxy Review Committee, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 30-33)
        Lowi, Theodore J.; Ehrenberg, Ronald G.; Stewart, Patricia Carry; Divestment
      - Trustees - Proxy Review Committee Report, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 34)
      - Trustees - Committee on Land Grant and State College Affairs, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 35)
      - Trustees - Committee on Status of Women and Minorities, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 36)
      - Trustee Meetings- General, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 37)
      - Trustee Executive Committee - Report of the President, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 38-43)
        Barker, Robert
      - Trustee Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Trustees - October Board - Report of the President, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 2-5)
      - Trustees - November Board, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 6)
      - Trustees - Executive Committee - December, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 7-8)
      - Trustees - Executive Committee - January, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 9)
      - Trustees - January Board, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 10)
      - Trustees - Report of the President, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 11)
      - Trustees - Executive Committee - February, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 12)
      - Trustees - Executive Committee - March, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 13)
      - Trustees - March Board - Report of the President, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 14-16)
      - Trustees - Executive Committee - April, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 17)
      - Trustees - Executive Committee - May - Report of the President, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 18-19)
      - Trustees - May Board - Report of the President, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 20-23)
      - Trustees - Executive Committee - June - Report of the President, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 24-25)
      - President's Report, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 26)
    - University Assembly
      - University Assembly - General, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 27-31)
      - Advisory Committee on Responsible Speech and Expression, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 32)
      - Employee Assembly, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 33-35)
      - Student Assembly, 1988-89 (Box 192, Folder 36-40)
      - Gearing and Review Boards, 1987-89 (Box 192, Folder 41)
      - Campus Planning Committee, 1984-89 (Box 192, Folder 42-43)
  - Provost's Office
    - Office of the Provost
      - General, 1982-89 (Box 194, Folder 1-3)
        Campus planning.
      - Academic Personnel, 1987-89 (Box 194, Folder 4)
        Williams, L. Pearce
      - General, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 5-6)
        Freedom of speech; "Photo Policy"
      - Lowenthal (ACB Bd) - Missions and Goals, Planning for the Future, 1987-89 (Box 194, Folder 7-8)
        Cornell University Mission Statement
      - Courses on Racism - Growth, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 9)
      - Executive Budget Group Minutes, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 10)
      - Budget Meetings, Deans and Administrators; Planning, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 11-12)
        Campus planning
      - Budget Planning Meeting, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 13-15)
      - Dean's Half-Day Sessions, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 16-17)
      - Deans/Provost Meeting, 1986 (Box 194, Folder 18)
        Computers; Salaries
      - Endowed Budget Papers, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 19-20)
      - Endowed Budget Papers, 1989-90 (Box 194, Folder 21)
      - Faculty Salary Recovery, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 22)
      - Admissions - General, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 23-24)
        Murphy, Susan H.
      - Enrollments (Targets), 1988 (Box 194, Folder 25)
      - Admissions Complaints/Recommendations, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 26-29)
      - Financial Aid, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 30-31)
      - Tuition - Cornell Tradition, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 32)
      - Division of Biological Sciences, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 33-34)
      - Isles of Shoals, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 35)
      - Institute for African Development, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 36)
      - Library, 1988-89 (Box 194, Folder 37-38)
        Seznec, Alain; Gates, Henry Louis; Library expansion
      - Library, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 1-3)
        Seznec, Alain; Lynn, M. Stuart; Information technologies; Salaries
      - Olin Library Users' Group, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 4)
      - Library - Meeting in NYC, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 5)
      - Library - Academic Affairs, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 6)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG), 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 7)
      - Africana Center, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 8)
      - Undergraduate Minor in African Studies, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 9)
      - Black Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 10)
        Black Students United
      - Educational Opportunity, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 11)
      - Minority Education, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 12-13)
        Hines, May
      - Native Americans, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 14)
        American Indian Program
      - Vice President for Computing, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 15-16)
        Lynn, M. Stuart; Cornell Information Technologies
      - Computational Science/STDT Information System Survey, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 17)
      - Computer Virus, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 18)
        Morris, Robert T.
      - Computer Virus - Final Report, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 19-20)
      - Computer Security, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 21)
      - Vice President for Planning, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 22)
      - Cornell Abroad, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 22-24)
      - Hispanics/Hispanic American Studies Program/Asian-American Studies/Southeast Asia Program/Southeast Asia, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 25)
      - Johnson Art Museum/Laboratory of Ornithology/CIPA, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 26)
      - Cornell University Press - Space Analysis, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 27)
      - Vice President Larry Palmer, Lsrry, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 28-31)
      - ROTC/Freshman Writing, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 32)
      - Annual Reports Miscellaneous, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 33-38)
      - President's Retreats, 1988-89 (Box 195, Folder 39-40)
      - Recruitment Report, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 41)
      - Career Center, 1987-88 (Box 195, Folder 42)
      - Education and the Community, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 1)
      - Health Careers/Learning Skills Center, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 2)
      - Washington Programs/Summer Session, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 3)
      - Undergraduate STDT Complaints, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 4)
      - Commission on Undergraduate Education/Cornell Scholars, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 5)
      - Commission on Undergraduate Education - Subcommittee on Support for Instruction, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 6)
      - Science, Technology and Society, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 7)
      - Vice President for Research, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 8-9)
      - Mitsui and Company, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 10-11)
        Kazusa Project
      - Strategic Technologies at Cornell University/ Corporate Liaison Committee, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 12)
      - Technology Transfer, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 13-14)
        Boorstein, Allen L.
      - Transition Authority, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 15)
      - Ofir Moreno/Nanofabrication Facility/OPT MOCVD Laboratory/Electronics, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 16)
      - Biotechnology Program (Kodak), 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 17-19)
      - Arecibo, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 20-21)
      - Radiophysics and Space Research - Palomar Observatory, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 22)
        Sagan, Carl; Divestment
      - Center for Environmental Research, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 23)
      - Center for International Studies, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 24)
      - CLEARS (Cornell Laboratory for Environmental Applications of Remote Sensing), 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 25-26)
      - CISER (Cornell Institute for Social and Economic Research, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 27)
      - Peace Studies Program, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 28)
      - Materials Science Center, 1988-89 (Box 196, Folder 29)